{"category":"Production Line", "auditType":"Production","questions": [{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "What item is being produced on this line?", "correctAnswer" : "ANY", "answers": ["BLENDER","BLOWER","BREADMAKER","CAN OPENER","COMPACT FREEZER","COMPACT REFRIDGERATOR","COUNTERTOP GRILL","COUNTERTOP ICEMAKER","DEHUMIDIFIER","DESKTOP-WALL MOUNT FAN","DRIP COFFEE MAKER","ELECTRIC KNIFE","FOOD PROCESSOR","GRIDDLE","HAND MIXER","HEATER","IRON","JOBSITE SAW","JUICER","MICROWAVE","PORTABLE AIR CONDITIONER","RICE COOKER","SLOT TOASTER","SLOW COOKER","SOUNDBAR","STRING TRIMMER","TOASTER OVEN","WAFFLE IRON","WINDOW AIR CONDITIONER"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Do approved work instructions exist for the item being produced?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Is line clean?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Is line free of obstructions that  would limit movement or people or products?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Is line staffing no more than work instruction allocation?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "If PPE is required, is PPE present?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["n/a", "Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "If PPE is present, is it in good working condition?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["n/a", "Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Are all required supplies present?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Is all required special equipment or material present?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["n/a", "Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Are all required gaylords present and being used for their assigned waste?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Is there clearly defined and utilized WIP storage areas between resource centers?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Ia there a clearly defined and utilized item quarantine area?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["n/a", "Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Are quarantined item's issues clearly displayed?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["n/a", "Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Is breakdown performing all required tasks in work instruction approved sequence?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Is testing performing all required tasks in work instruction approved sequence?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Is cleaning performing all required tasks in work instruction approved sequence?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Is packing performing all required tasks in work instruction approved sequence?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Does QC have approved quality standard available for item being produced?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},{"section" : "n/a", "question" : "Is QC performing all required tasks in work instruction approved sequence?", "correctAnswer" : "Yes", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]}]}
